Experimental College Records UA044
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Course files, 1965 -- 2012; UA044.003; 22.8 Linear Feet
  - EXP 097 S71 Seminar in Continuing Education, 1971; UA044.003.015.00049; Laskaris, Judy; Knable, Bobbie (Box 15)
  - EXP 097 F71, S72 Seminar in Continuing Education, 1971 -- 1972; UA044.003.015.00050; Lipsky, Suzanne (Box 15)
  - EXP 097 F69 Culture and Human Behavior, 1969; UA044.003.015.00051; Bestor, William (Box 15)
  - EXP 098 S74 Psychophysiology of Sleep and Dreams, 1974; UA044.003.015.00052; Dushan, Steve; Silverman, Matthew (Box 15)
  - EXP 098 F72, S74 Junk Art for Kids, 1972 -- 1974; UA044.003.015.00053; Wolsky, Betty (Box 15)
  - EXP 098 F70 Dutch, 1970; UA044.003.015.00054; De Vries, Mary Lou (Box 15)
  - EXP 099 F74, S75, F75, S76 Auditing for Breadth, 1974 -- 1976; UA044.003.015.00055; Gittleman, Robyn (Box 15)
  - EXP 099 S73 Tufts Next Decade, 1973; UA044.003.015.00056; Nunn, Jack (Box 15)
  - EXP 099 S74 Alexander Technique of Kinesthetic Perception, 1974; UA044.003.015.00057; Jones, Frank (Box 15)
  - EXP 099 F72 Synetics, 1972; UA044.003.015.00058; Gordon, William J. J. (Box 15)
  - EXP 099 F70 Technology and Society, 1970; UA044.003.015.00059; Sussman, Martin; Wells, William; Bedau, Hugo Adam (Box 15)
  - EXP 099 F70 Chinese, 1970; UA044.003.015.00060; Ching, Yu-pei (Box 15)
  - EXP 099A S71 Continuation of 99 Chinese, 1971; UA044.003.015.00061; Ching, Yu-pei (Box 15)
  - EXP 099 F71 Beginning Mandarin Chinese, 1971; UA044.003.015.00062; Chen, Hui-p'ing (Box 15)
  - EXP 099A F71 Advanced Mandarin Chinese, 1971; UA044.003.015.00063; Ching, Yu-pei (Box 15)
  - EXP 100 F70, S71, F71 Information Sources for Research, 1970 -- 1971; UA044.003.015.00064; Beal, George (Box 15)
  - EXP 101 F69 Participant in Discovery, 1969; UA044.003.015.00065; Sussman, M. V. (Coordinator) (Box 15)
  - EXP 101 F70 Participant in Discovery, 1970; UA044.003.015.00066; Sussman, Martin (Box 15)
  - EXP 101-102 S71 Participant in Discovery, 1971; UA044.003.015.00067; Sussman, Martin (Box 15)
  - EXP 101-102 F71, S72 Participant in Discovery, 1971 -- 1972; UA044.003.015.00068; Sussman, Martin (Box 15)
  - EXP 102 S70 Participant in Discovery, 1970; UA044.003.015.00069; Sussman, Martin (Box 15)
  - EXP 191 F74, S75, S76 Independent Study, 1974 -- 1976; UA044.003.015.00070; Gittleman, Robyn (Box 15)
  - EXP 194S, 193F, 193S S75, F75, S76 Community Apprenticeships, 1975 -- 1976; UA044.003.015.00071; Rubel, Barbara (Box 15)
  - EXP 193F, 194F S73, S74, F74 Community Apprenticeships, 1973 -- 1974; UA044.003.015.00072; Slapikoff, Saul (Box 15)
  - EXP 195A S69 Study Group: Metaphysics and Physics Collision, 1969; UA044.003.015.00073; Tessman, Associate Professor (Box 15)
  - EXP 091 F69 New French Narrative Cinema, 1969; UA044.003.015.00074; Haycock, Joel (Box 15)
  - 009 S'67 Trends in Contemporary Art Forms, 1967; UA044.003.015.00075; Welber, Michael (Box 15)
  - 009 S'67 The Short Story as an Art Form, 1967; UA044.003.015.00076; Demas, Corinne (Box 15)
  - 009 S'67 The American City, 1967; UA044.003.015.00077; Swope, William A. (Box 15)
  - 009 F'67 From Catharsis to Communication- A Workshop in Writing Freshman Seminar, 1967; UA044.003.015.00078; Demas, Corinne (Box 15)
  - 009 F'67 Ecology Freshman Seminar, 1967; UA044.003.015.00079; Ciampa, George R. (Box 15)
  - 9C F'67 The Ethnic Group in the Urban Center Freshman Seminar, 1967; UA044.003.015.00080; DiMuro, Edward J. (Box 15)
  - 9E F'67 Introduction to Looking Freshman Seminar, 1967; UA044.003.015.00081; Skilken, Lynn (Box 15)
  - 9F F'67 Poverty in America in the 1960's Freshman Seminar, 1967; UA044.003.016.00001; Glynn, Thomas P. III (Box 16)
  - 9C F'67 Religion and Contemporary Ethics Freshman Seminar, 1967; UA044.003.016.00002; Shreve, Anita (Box 16)
  - 9H S'68 The Art of the Absurd Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00003; Dahl, Linda Alice; Heiberg, Karen Anne (Box 16)
  - 9L S'68 Herman Hesse's Visions of the Ideal Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00004; Mann, Sharon S. (Box 16)
  - 9J S'68 The Dilema of Environmental Quality Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00005; Good, Deirdre; Sammons, David; Peterson, Sheila; Pivorin, Edward (Box 16)
  - 9K S'68 Greek Tragedy Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00006; Cappuccino, Carleton C. (Box 16)
  - 9M S'68 Modern French Poetry Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00007; Zimmerman, Marilyn (Box 16)
  - 9P S'68 Science and Human Values Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00008; Coburn, Erica; Drazen, Jeffrey (Box 16)
  - 9Q S'68 Some Aspects of the Interrelationship Between Man and Society Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00009; Gerraughty, Roddy F. (Box 16)
  - 9R S'68 Toward an Appretiation of the Seashore Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00010; Nove, John (Box 16)
  - 9G F'70 "A Study of SElected Issues in American Criminal Law", 1970; UA044.003.016.00011; Yarrow, Steven (Box 16)
  - 9S S'68 The Medium of Journalism-Literary and Informative Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00012; Harris, Diana (Box 16)
  - 9T S'68 Environmental Awareness Through Sensory Perception Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00013; Livingston, Sherrill G.; Lewis, Lanny; Silver, Susan R. (Box 16)
  - 9V S'68 The Negro Today Freshman Seminar, 1968; UA044.003.016.00014; Jordan, Charles; Smith, Jacquelyn (Box 16)
  - 9F F'70 "Nonviolent Revolution", 1970; UA044.003.016.00015; Schulter, Michael (Box 16)
  - 9E F'70 "Competitive Debating", 1970; UA044.003.016.00016; Scheur, Barry (Box 16)
  - 9D F'70 "Judaism in America from Within and Without", 1970; UA044.003.016.00017; Meyer, James; Strazzulla, Regina (Box 16)
  - 9C F'70 "Napoleonic Wars - A Military and Political View", 1970; UA044.003.016.00018; Chisholm, David (Box 16)
  - 9A F'70 "Miliary - Industrial Complex", 1970; UA044.003.016.00019; Ayervais, Neil (Box 16)
  - EXP 01S, Spring 1989: Confucius/Taoism/100 Schools, Jonathan Herman, UA044.003.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - EXP 01F, Fall 1988: Obscenity in Literature, Leslie Dunton-Downer, UA044.003.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - EXP 01S, Spring 1987: Pindar and Baseball, Jeffrey Carnes, UA044.003.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02S, Spring 1987: Introduction to Egyptian heiroglyphics, Ann Roth, UA044.003.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02F, Fall 1987: Christ, Anti-Christ, and Culture, M. Scot Miller, UA044.003.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02S, Spring 1984, Spring 1985: Jack Kerouac and the Beats, Ronna Johnson, 1984 -- 1985; UA044.003.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02S, Spring 1982: O Pioneers! Literature of the Prairies, Adam Ward Rome, UA044.003.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02S, Spring 1981: Science Fiction: Literature and Writing, Kathleen Romer, UA044.003.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02F, Fall 1981: Literature of Love and Erotica, Patricia Tanzosh, UA044.003.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02S, Spring 1980: From Dune to Dragonrider: Society and the Individual in Science Fiction, UA044.003.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02S, Spring 1979: Literature and Origins of the Small Presses, Roberta Kalechofsky, UA044.003.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02F, Fall 1979: The Child in Literature, Karla Gustafson, UA044.003.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02S, Spring 1978: Contemporary American Fiction, Charles Gill, UA044.003.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02S, Spring 1977: The Theatre in Ireland, Michael Brady, UA044.003.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02F, Fall 1977: Black Literature, Joyce Freedom, UA044.003.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - EXP 02S, Spring 1976: American Maritime Art and Literature, Joseph Goodman, UA044.003.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03S, Spring 1987: Tales from the Raj, Paul Toomey, UA044.003.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03F, Fall 1986: Understanding Leonardo, Antoinette Prince, UA044.003.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03F, Fall 1985: "Theaology": Contemporary Interest in Goddesses, Emily Culpepper, UA044.003.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03S, Spring 1984: Twentieth-Century Humor, Josh Rosenfeld and Robert Burnett, UA044.003.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03S, Spring 1982: Public and Private Writing, Patricia Baudoin, UA044.003.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03S, Spring 1981: American Political Theatre, Steven Yakutis, UA044.003.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03S, Spring 1980: Holocaust Literature, Michael Rauchman and Ariane May, UA044.003.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03S, Spring 1978: Exploring Tolkien, Edward Powers, UA044.003.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03F, Fall 1977, Fall 1978: Children's Literature, Karla Gustafson, 1977 -- 1978; UA044.003.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03S, Spring 1976: Batik, Allyson Jo Rymland, UA044.003.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - EXP 03S, Spring 1976: Autobiography and Fiction, Nancy Kline Piore, UA044.003.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04S, Spring 1987: Introduction to the Art of Russia, Musya Glants, UA044.003.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04S, Spring 1986: Necessary Bread, Sylvia Wright, UA044.003.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04S, Spring 1983: Visions of the Holocaust, Alan Rosen, UA044.003.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04S, Spring 1982: Monsters, Villains, and the Creative Genius, Lin Haire-Sargeant, UA044.003.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04S, Spring 1981: Medieval Mystery Plays in Practice, Nicholas Linfield, UA044.003.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04F, Fall 1981: Walt Whitman and Friends, Rudy Kikel, UA044.003.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04S, Spring 1980: Eastern Philosophical Literature and its Western Counterparts, Peter Fuhrman, UA044.003.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04S, Spring 1979: Fundamentals of Book Publishing, Constance Putnam, UA044.003.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04F, Fall 1979: Self-Realization through the Art Experience, Guillemine de Lacoste, UA044.003.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04S, Spring 1978: Women in Drama and Theatre, Michael Brady and Shirley Staples, UA044.003.018.00037 (Box 18)
  - EXP 04S, Spring 1976: Calligraphy, Leslie Young, UA044.003.018.00038 (Box 18)
  - EXP 05S, Spring 1989: The Evolution of the Gay Hero in American Fiction, Bennett Singer, UA044.003.018.00039 (Box 18)
  - EXP 05S, Spring 1987: Memory and Imagination in the Nuclear Age, Michael Perlman, UA044.003.018.00040 (Box 18)
  - EXP 05F, Fall 1987: Latino Poetry in the United States, (EXP 06S, Spring 1987: Latino Poetry and Social Issues in the United States), Martin Espada, 1986 -- 1987; UA044.003.018.00041 (Box 18)
  - EXP 05F (ML93), Fall 1986: Introduction to Spoken Arabic, James Broderick, UA044.003.018.00042 (Box 18)
  - EXP 05F, Fall 1985: Murder They Wrote: From Poe to Parker, Kathleen Joyce and Sara Frost, UA044.003.018.00043 (Box 18)
  - EXP 05S, Spring 1984: Novels into Film, Jeff Strauss, UA044.003.018.00044 (Box 18)
  - EXP 05F, Fall 1982: Sail Ho! The Literature of the Sea, James Stavridis, UA044.003.018.00045 (Box 18)
  - EXP 05S, Spring 1981: Man and His Existence, Joseph Audette and Stephan Bamberger, UA044.003.018.00046 (Box 18)
  - EXP 05S, Spring 1976: Binding Books: an Introduction, Philip Zuckerman, UA044.003.018.00047 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1989: The Schlemiel in America, David Chack and Carol Ely, UA044.003.018.00048 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1987: The Search for the Center: Zen and Western Thought, John Poque, UA044.003.018.00049 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1986: Sound, Word and Image: the Temporal Arts in Transition, Guy Buckle, UA044.003.018.00050 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1984: Children of Violence: the Vision of Doris Lessing, Diane Wynne, UA044.003.018.00051 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1983: What's So Funny? An Interdisciplinary Approach to Humor, Alfie Kohn, UA044.003.018.00052 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1981: Surface Design on Fabrics, Muriel Angelil, UA044.003.018.00053 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1980: Law, Order and Literature, Jane Ginsburg, UA044.003.018.00054 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06F, Fall 1980: Collage, Giselle Maya Sieburth, UA044.003.018.00055 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1979: Weaving as an Art Form, Eve Jessen Linson, UA044.003.018.00056 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1978: Graphics Workshop, Laurie Polster, UA044.003.018.00057 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1977: How to Build a Gothic Cathedral, UA044.003.018.00058 (Box 18)
  - EXP 06S, Spring 1976: Beethoven, Robert Dorian, UA044.003.018.00059 (Box 18)
  - EXP 07S, Spring 1989: Martin Heidegger's Being and Time, Kerry Dugan, UA044.003.018.00060 (Box 18)
  - EXP 07F, Fall 1987: Collage, Robin Reba Goodman, UA044.003.018.00061 (Box 18)
  - EXP 07F, Fall 1986: Introduction to Editing, Constance Putnam, UA044.003.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - EXP 07F, Fall 1982: The Pacific World, Murry Martin, UA044.003.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - EXP 07S, Spring 1980: Off-Loom Weaving, Muriel Angelil, UA044.003.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - EXP 07F, Fall 1978: Egg Tempera Painting, Kim Pashko, UA044.003.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - EXP 07S, Spring 1977: Layout and Design, Sandra Schafer, UA044.003.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - EXP 07F, Fall 1976: Beginning Ear Training, David Sussman, UA044.003.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - EXP 07S, Spring 1976: Music and Computers, Arthur Pike, UA044.003.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08F, Fall 1987: Flights of Fancy for Mind and Body, UA044.003.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08S, Spring 1987: Intermedia Workshop, Gary Duehr, UA044.003.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08S, Spring 1986: About Creating, Reid Robbins, UA044.003.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08S, Spring 1984: Asian American Literature, Elizabeth Toupin and Ruth Hsiao, UA044.003.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08S, Spring 1983: Exploring the Avant Garde, Mark Harvey, UA044.003.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08S, Spring 1982: Walter Bauer, Painting on the Side, UA044.003.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08F, Fall 1981: Stained Glass, A Personal and Environmental Approach, UA044.003.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08S, Spring 1981: Beginning Rigid Heddle Weaving, Bette Robert, UA044.003.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08S, Spring 1980: Face to Face: Expressing Character through a Sculptural Portrait, UA044.003.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08F, Fall 1978: Art in Boston, Allyson Sheckler and Evelyn Staudinger, UA044.003.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08F, Fall 1977: Off-Loom Weaving, Deborah Ann Colburn, UA044.003.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08S, Spring 1977: African Art, Peggy Wagner, UA044.003.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - EXP 08F, Fall 1976: Three Faces of Motion, Barry Feiler, UA044.003.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - EXP 09S, Spring 1986: Imagination by Design, Deborah Dunham, UA044.003.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - EXP 09S, Spring 1981: Environmental Sculpture, Beth Galston, UA044.003.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - EXP 09S, Spring 1980: Calligraphy, Hajar Gross, UA044.003.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - EXP 09S, Spring 1979: The Artist's Point of View: American Realism, Ellen Miller, UA044.003.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - EXP 09S, Spring 1977: How to Listen to Jazz, Lewis Porter, UA044.003.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - EXP 09F, Fall 1976: Behavior Modification, David Swinney, UA044.003.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - EXP 10S, Spring 1989: African-American Art, Rosalyn Elder, UA044.003.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - EXP 10F, Fall 1988: Making Books for Children, Jill Smillow, UA044.003.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - EXP 10S, Spring 1986: Self-Defense for Women, Nancy Sableski, UA044.003.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - EXP 10S, Spring 1981: Contemporary Art: What is It? Who Makes It?, Robert Storr, UA044.003.019.00030 (Box 19)
  - EXP 10F, Fall 1979: Explorations in Singing: A Workshop in Musical Comedy, Mary Ann Platz, UA044.003.019.00031 (Box 19)
  - EXP 10S, Spring 1979: Musical Theater as Art, Stephen Pietrantoni, UA044.003.019.00032 (Box 19)
  - EXP 11S, Spring 1988: Portraits and Other Things: Society, Politics, and the Human Condition, Paul Stopforth, UA044.003.019.00033 (Box 19)
  - EXP 11S, Spring 1988: Portraits and Other Things: Society, Politics, and the Human Condition, Paul Stopforth - slides, UA044.003.019.00034 (Box 19)
    this file contains slides used in EXP 11S, Spring 1988
  - EXP 11S, Spring 1983 (EXP 12F, Fall 1983/ EXP 13S, Spring 1986): Fresco Painting: History and Practice, Alston Stoney Conley, 1983 -- 1986; UA044.003.019.00035 (Box 19)
  - EXP 11S, Spring 1982 (EXP 11F, Fall 1982): Carving in Stone and Wood, Bernadette D'Amore, UA044.003.019.00036 (Box 19)
  - EXP 11F, Fall 1978: Color Photography Without a Darkroom, Anne Bray, UA044.003.019.00037 (Box 19)
  - EXP 11F, Fall 1977: Build Your Own Home, Arthur Bradbury, UA044.003.019.00038 (Box 19)
  - EXP 11S, Spring 1976: The Woman Athlete, Julie Eades, UA044.003.019.00039 (Box 19)
  - EXP 12S, Spring 1988: Conduction, Comprovisation: Contemporary Methods of Composition for the Improvisor, UA044.003.019.00040 (Box 19)
  - EXP 12S, Spring 1987: Architecture in the Environment, Susan Stuebing and Victor Olgyay, UA044.003.019.00041 (Box 19)
  - EXP 12F, Fall 1984 (EXP 12S, Spring 1985): Architectural Design Studio, J. Brozek, 1984 -- 1985; UA044.003.019.00042 (Box 19)
  - EXP 12S, Spring 1983: Casting with Paper, Jeffrey Gerlinger, UA044.003.019.00043 (Box 19)
  - EXP 12S, Spring 1982: Alternative Photographic Image Making, Margaret Harrigan, UA044.003.019.00044 (Box 19)
  - EXP 12S, Spring 1980: Jazz and Show Choir, Gloria Malfeld, UA044.003.019.00045 (Box 19)
  - EXP 12S, Spring 1978/Spring 1979: Photography: Toward Self-Expressions, Susan Ehrens, 1978 -- 1979; UA044.003.019.00046 (Box 19)
  - EXP 12F, Fall 1976: New Street Photography, Kent Phelan, UA044.003.019.00047 (Box 19)
  - EXP 13F, Fall 1989: Percussion and Steel Pan Workshop, Mackie Burnette, UA044.003.019.00048 (Box 19)
  - EXP 13F, Fall 1983: Elements of Architectural, Paul Glassman, UA044.003.019.00049 (Box 19)
  - EXP 13S, Spring 1976: Androgyny: Open Hand and Fist, Marlin Potash, UA044.003.019.00050 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14S, Spring 1988: The Oriental Brush: the Art of Chinese and Japanese Calligraphy, Michael Biales, UA044.003.019.00051 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14F, Fall 1987: Comparative Vertebrate Anatomy, David Krauss, UA044.003.019.00052 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14S, Spring 1987: Home: the Meaning of Space in Domestic Architecture, Tim McKenna and Janine Wong, UA044.003.019.00053 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14F, Fall 1986: Making Movies with a Personal Computer, Buki Esuruoso, UA044.003.019.00054 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14S, Spring 1985, Spring 1986: An Introduction to Watercolor, Seymour Simmons, 1985 -- 1986; UA044.003.019.00055 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14F, Fall 1984: An Introduction to Calligraphy, Carolyn Reese, UA044.003.019.00056 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14S, Spring 1984: Exploring Sculpture, Bernadette D'Amore, UA044.003.019.00057 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14F, Fall 1979: Visualization and Photographic Symbol, Debra Strick, UA044.003.019.00058 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14F, Fall 1977: Introduction to Architectural Design, Ed Ducek and Nancy Goodwin, UA044.003.019.00059 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14F, Fall 1976: Women and Violence, Freada Klein, UA044.003.019.00060 (Box 19)
  - EXP 14S, Spring 1976: Homosexual Behavior, Bob Meade, UA044.003.019.00061 (Box 19)
  - EXP 15F, Fall 1989: Paperpulp Painting, Muriel Angelil, UA044.003.019.00062 (Box 19)
  - EXP 15S, Spring 1989: Fundamentals of Chinese Medicine, Jim Martin, UA044.003.019.00063 (Box 19)
  - EXP 15S, Spring 1984: T'ai Chi, David Zucker, UA044.003.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - EXP 15S, Spring 1978: Combat and Circus, Jan Kirschner, UA044.003.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - EXP 15S, Spring 1977: Concepts of Success, Lucretia Gruber and Bruce Paley, UA044.003.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - EXP 15F, Fall 1976: New Women - New Men, A.L. Palubinskas, UA044.003.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - EXP 15S, Spring 1976: Physiology of Consciousness, Philip Lansky, UA044.003.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16F, Fall 1987: Science Technology and the Law, Richard Miller, UA044.003.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16S, Spring 1987: Space Exploration, Maria Sakellariadou, UA044.003.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16S, Spring 1986: Unraveling Cognitive Mysteries, Craig Decker, UA044.003.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16S, Spring 1985: Portrait Photography, Birgitta Ralston, UA044.003.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16S, Spring 1983: Improvisation, Christopher Payton, UA044.003.020.00010 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16S, Spring 1981: Mime, Shep Barnett, UA044.003.020.00011 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16F, Fall 1979: Conversational Armenian, UA044.003.020.00012 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16F, Fall 1978: Wilderness Survival and Mountaineering First Aid, Jim DiVirgilio and Jay Minkoff, UA044.003.020.00013 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16S, Spring 1978: Beginning Mime, John Collins, UA044.003.020.00014 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16F, Fall 1977: T'ai Chi: The Mind and Body, Ralph Ward, UA044.003.020.00015 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16F, Fall 1976: Exploring the Human Body, Anna Gruyer, UA044.003.020.00016 (Box 20)
  - EXP 16S, Spring 1976: Transpersonal Psychologies, William Crittenden, UA044.003.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - EXP 17S, Spring 1989: Justice and the Environment, Michael Fowler, UA044.003.020.00018 (Box 20)
  - EXP 17F, Fall 1988: Human Factors in Space Exploration, Benton Lawson, UA044.003.020.00019 (Box 20)
  - EXP 17S, Spring 1988: The Neuroscience of Learning and Memory, Turhan Canli, UA044.003.020.00020 (Box 20)
  - EXP 17F, Fall 1983: Expressive Self, Paula Josa-Jones, UA044.003.020.00021 (Box 20)
  - EXP 17S, Spring 1982: Creativity: a Theatre Workshop, Marc Maislen, UA044.003.020.00022 (Box 20)
  - EXP 17F, 19F, Fall 1980/Fall 1982: Postural Transformation (EXP 17S, Spring 1981: The Psychology of Movement), Daniel Orlansky, 1980 -- 1982; UA044.003.020.00023 (Box 20)
  - EXP 17S, Spring 1978: Jogging, Running, Racing, John Pistone, UA044.003.020.00024 (Box 20)
  - EXP 17S, Spring 1977: The Study and Experience of Meditation, Tom Giles, UA044.003.020.00025 (Box 20)
  - EXP 18F, Fall 1987: Workfuture: the Impact of Information Technology, John Austin, UA044.003.020.00026 (Box 20)
  - EXP 18S, Spring 1987: Garden in Peril: American Environmental Thought from 1830, Kathleen Wadden, UA044.003.020.00027 (Box 20)
  - EXP 18S, Spring 1986: Solar Energy for Everyone, Gregory Barker, UA044.003.020.00028 (Box 20)
  - EXP 18F, Fall 1986: Can Machines Think?, Panayiotis Theodossopoulos, UA044.003.020.00029 (Box 20)
  - EXP 18S, Spring 1985: Bhar Natyam: Classical Indian Dance, Kaplana Seshadri, UA044.003.020.00030 (Box 20)
  - EXP 18S, Spring 1977: Perceptual Development: A Kid's Eye View of the World, Penny Prather, UA044.003.020.00031 (Box 20)
  - EXP 18S, Spring 1976: Kinesthetic Perception, Richard Brown, UA044.003.020.00032 (Box 20)
  - EXP 19S, Spring 1989: Society and Technology in Ancient Greece and Rome, Owen Doonan, UA044.003.020.00033 (Box 20)
  - EXP 19S, Spring 1988/Spring 1989: Science and Medical Writing, John Lauerman, 1988 -- 1989; UA044.003.020.00034 (Box 20)
  - EXP 19S, Spring 1986: Casualties in the Workplace: Occupational Health and Safety, Philip Korman, UA044.003.020.00035 (Box 20)
  - EXP 19F, Fall 1985: Fantastic Art of the Future, Karen Burke, UA044.003.020.00036 (Box 20)
  - EXP 19F, Fall 1983: Health, Stress, and Lifestyle, Rachel Brooks and Thomas Thrall, UA044.003.020.00037 (Box 20)
  - EXP 19S, Spring 1982: Making Music with Children, Lucille Magliozzi, UA044.003.020.00038 (Box 20)
  - EXP 19F, Fall 1978: New Orleans Jazz, Hank Faunce, UA044.003.020.00039 (Box 20)
  - EXP 19S, Spring 1977: Women and Madness, Susan E. Goodman, UA044.003.020.00040 (Box 20)
  - EXP 19S, Spring 1976: One Brain Two Minds, Max Hirshkowitz, UA044.003.020.00041 (Box 20)
  - EXP 20S, Spring 1989: Latin American Passages, Pedro Garcia-Matias, UA044.003.020.00042 (Box 20)
  - EXP 20S, Spring 1988: The Darwinian Revolution, Ross Feldberg, UA044.003.020.00043 (Box 20)
  - EXP 20F, Fall 1981: Popular Music in America, Thomas Warner, UA044.003.020.00044 (Box 20)
  - EXP 20F, Fall 1977/Spring 1978/Spring 1979/Spring 1979/Fall 1980: Modern Jazz: History and Analysis, Lewis Porter, 1977 -- 1980; UA044.003.020.00045 (Box 20)
  - EXP 20S, Spring 1976: Brain Control, Barry Skoff, UA044.003.020.00046 (Box 20)
  - EXP 21F (SPN 001X), Fall 1988: Spanish Through the Natural Approach, Jenifer Burkett-Picker, UA044.003.020.00047 (Box 20)
  - EXP 21F, Fall 1985: Introduction to Architecture and Solar Design, Jane Katz, UA044.003.020.00048 (Box 20)